

+60 179641020 gruchikaid@gmail.com

www.amazingstudent.com

<u>inkedIn</u>

SKILLS AutoCAD, 3Ds max, Sketchup, MS Office, problem solving, design understanding

ABOUT ME

Motivated and stalwart Interior Designer with 5+ year experience in delivering exceptional designs and coordinating executional services to the customer satisfaction and requirement. Conscientious and hardworking team player seeking to amplify skills by giving my best as a designer.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Interior Designer

Supporting client Glanz Industries Sdn, Bhd.

2018 - present

Complete interior concept And Exhibition booth designs with 2D Drafting, 3D images and material details

Interior Designer

Custom Furnish (Hinshitsu Manufacturing Pvt. Ltd)

2017 - 2018

Factory based modular furniture designing and interior designing

Associate Interior Designer

Vihange Interiors Pvt. Ltd

2015 - 2017

Complete interior solutions, conceptual designing and solutions

Freelance Interior Designer

Arctic Interiors (Hinshitsu Manufacturing Pvt. Ltd)

2014 - 2015

• Basic research for materials and hardware for renovation projects

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth | 21 April 1991

Address | KL Gateway Residency, Bangsar South, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Citizenship | Indian on dependent pass Languages | English, HIndi, Telugu

EDUCATION

Jawahar Lal Architecture and Fine Arts University | Hamstech Institute of Interior and Fashion Designing

- Diploma in Interior Designing - 2013-2015

Osmania University

- Bachelor of Engineering in Industrial Production - 2009 - 2013